Finding aid for Library (University of Michigan) Records, 1837 - 2013
Bentley Historical Library
- Director's Files, 1905-2013
  - Topical Files, 1905-1999
    - 1978-1988
      - Library (U of M)
        - Professional Evaluation Review Committee (PERC), 1980-1987 (Box 167)
        - Photoduplication Services, 1981-1987 (Box 167)
        - Planning, 1980; 1984-1988; 4 folders (Box 167)
        - Preservation/Conservation, 1984-1986 (Box 167)
        - Public Services, 1979-1987 (Box 167)
        - Public Services Council, 1985-1987 (Box 167)
        - Rare Books and Special Collections Department, 1982-1987 (Box 167)
        - Reference Department, 1986 (Box 167)
        - Reorganization, 1984 (Box 167)
        - Reserve Service, 1981-1982 (Box 168)
        - Scholars Program, 1984 (Box 168)
        - Library Science 791, Independent Study Course, 1984-1985 (Box 168)
        - Library Serials Study, 1979-1984 (Box 168)
        - Six Millionth Volume, 1983-1986 (Box 168)
        - State of the Library, Notes and Addresses, 1981-1987 (Box 168)
        - Systems Office and Planning, 1982-1988 (Box 168)
        - Undergraduate Library, 1981-1988 (Box 168)
        - Unit Heads, 1983-1984 (Box 168)
      - Library of Congress, 1978-1987; 2 folders (Box 168)
      - Library of Michigan, 1978-1987 (Box 168)
      - Linked Systems Project (LSP), 1985-1987 (Box 168)
      - Litigation, Laird-Dougherty, 1979-1981 (Box 196)
      - Merit Review Evaluations (Personnel), 1981-1987 (Box 196)
      - Merit Computer Network, 1986 (Box 168)
      - Michigan Alliance for the Conservation of Cultural Heritage, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 168)
      - Michigan Annual Giving Program, 1984 (Box 168)
      - Michigan Center for the Book, 1986-1987 (Box 168)
      - Michigan Council of State Colleges and University Library Directors, 1979-1987; 5 folders (Box 168)
      - Michigan Historical Collections
        - 1979-1981 (Box 196)
        - 1983-1985 (Box 168)
      - Michigan Information Transfer Source (MITS), 1979-1989; 3 folders (Box 168)
      - Michigan Library Association
        - General, 1981; 1983-1988; 2 folders (Box 168)
        - "Publishing the Journal Article,", 1981-1982 (Box 168)
      - Michigan Library Consortium, 1978-1988; 10 folders (Box 169)
      - Michigan State University, 1979-1984 (Box 169)
      - MIDwest Region LibrAry NeTwork (MIDLANT), 1978-1980; 2 folders (Box 169)
      - Michigan University
        - Administrative Systems Office, 1978-1984 (Box 169)
        - Affirmative Action Programs, 1979-1981 (Box 169)
        - Business Administration Library, 1979-1981 (Box 169)
        - Center for South and Southeast Asian Studies, 1981 (Box 169)
        - College of Literature, Science and the Arts, Library Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 169)
        - Communications Seminar, 1982 (Box 169)
        - Institute of Science and Technology, 1984-85 (Box 169)
        - Library
          - Acquisitions System, 1982 (Box 169)
          - Administration, 1978; 1983 (Box 169)
          - Administrative Personnel Evaluations, 1979-1980 (Box 196)
          - Automated Circulation System Proposal, 1978 (Box 170)
          - Cabinet, Minutes, 1979-1986; 13 folders (Box 170)
          - Circulation System, 1980-1981 (Box 170)
          - Classification Evaluation Committee (Personnel), 1978-1979 (Box 170)
          - Collection Development, 1980-1982 (Box 170)
          - Committees, Miscellaneous, 1978; 1985 (Box 170)
          - Database Coordinating Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 170)
          - Design of the University Library Bibliographic Database, 1979-1980 (Box 170)
          - Director's Assembly, 1983-1985 (Box 170)
          - Divisional Libraries
            - Art and Architecture, 1978 (Box 171)
            - Asia, 1982 (Box 171)
            - Biological Station, 1982 (Box 171)
            - Bureau of Government, 1982-1983 (Box 171)
            - Engineering-Transportation, 1980-1981 (Box 171)
            - Fine Arts, 1978-1980 (Box 171)
            - Museums, 1979-1981 (Box 171)
            - Music, 1979-1982 (Box 171)
            - Natural Science-Natural Resources, 1979-1981 (Box 171)
            - North Engineering, 1981 (Box 171)
            - Public Health, 1978 (Box 171)
            - Social Work, 1981 (Box 171)
          - Faculty Update, Newsletter, 1986 (Box 171)
          - Graduate Library. Publications, 1982 (Box 171)
          - Info-Skills, proposal, 1984 (Box 171)
          - Interlibrary Loan, 1980-1982 (Box 171)
          - Library Extension Service, 1980-1981 (Box 171)
          - Loan Code, 1978-1981 (Box 171)
          - Map Room, 1980 (Box 171)
          - Materials Selection Policy Committee, 1978-1980 (Box 171)
          - MIchigan Research LibrarY Network (MIRLYN) Automated Catalog
            - General, 1985-1986 (Box 171)
            - Implementation, 1987-1988; 3 folders (Box 171)
            - Training Guide, 1988 (Box 171)
          - Monthly Reports, Policy, 1984-1988 (Box 171)
          - Personnel Office, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 171)
          - Photoduplication Service, 1978 (Box 171)
          - Planning, 1979-1986; 7 folders (Box 171)
          - Preservation/Conservation, 1978-1982; 2 folders (Box 172)
          - Processing Time Study, 1978-1979 (Box 172)
          - Public Services Division, 1979-1981; 1985-1986 (Box 172)
          - Reorganization, 1984 (Box 172)
          - Residency Program, 1982-1986 (Box 172)
          - Serials Management Program, 1982-1983 (Box 172)
          - Shelflist Measurements, 1979-1983 (Box 172)
          - Staff, 1982-1987 (Box 172)
          - Staff Development Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 172)
          - Statistical Summaries, 1973-1986 (Box 172)
          - Systems Planning, 1978-1980 (Box 172)
          - The Advisory Group (TAG), 1978-1983; 4 folders (Box 172)
          - Taubman Medical Library, 1980-1981 (Box 172)
          - Technical Services
            - General, 1978-1980 (Box 172)
            - General, 1981-1982 (Box 196)
            - General, 1983-1988 (Box 172)
          - Thefts, 1981 (Box 172)
          - Undergraduate Library, 1979-1983 (Box 172)
        - Library Council, 1980-1985; 4 folders (Box 172)
        - Medical School, 1981 (Box 172)
        - Office of Capital Planning, 1979 (Box 173)
        - President of the University, 1979-1989 (Box 173)
        - School of Education, 1980 (Box 173)
        - School of Library Science
          - General, 1978-1987; 9 folders (Box 173)
          - Advisory Committee on CLR Grant, 1980-1981; 1986; 2 folders (Box 173)
          - Rosenberg, Prof. Victor, 1985 (Box 196)
        - University Press, 1972-1980 (Box 173)
        - University Seminar, 1985 (Box 173)
        - University Senate, 1980-1982 (Box 173)
        - Vice President and Chief Financial Officer, 1984-1985 (Box 173)
        - Vice President for Academic Affairs, 1982-1988; 4 folders (Box 173)
        - Vice President for Development and Communications, 1980-1988 (Box 173)
        - Vice President for Information Technology, 1984-1987 (Box 173)
        - Vice President for Research, 1981-1988 (Box 173)
        - Vice President for State Relations, 1980-1981 (Box 173)
        - Vice President for Student Affairs, 1985 (Box 173)
        - Vice Provost for Minority Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 173)
      - National Commission on Libraries and Informational Sciences, 1984-1986 (Box 173)
      - National Cooperative Cataloging Project (NCCP), 1985-1987 (Box 173)
      - National Periodicals Center, 1980 (Box 173)
      - New York Public Library, 1981-1985 (Box 173)
      - Northwestern Online Totally Integrated System (NOTIS)
        - General, 1982-1986 (Box 173)
        - System Specifications, 1985 (Box 173)
      - Oberlin College, 1983 (Box 173)
      - (OCLC) Online Computer Library Center System
        - General, 1978-1984; 2 folders (Box 173)
        - General, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 174)
        - Copyright Dispute, 1983-1984 (Box 174)
      - Office of University Audits, 1977; 1983 (Box 174)
      - Oregon University, 1978 (Box 174)
      - Overhead Cost Study, 1982-1986 (Box 174)
      - Program in American Culture, 1982 (Box 174)
      - Questionnaires/Surveys, 1961-1987 (Box 174)
      - Recommendations, 1978-1980 (Box 196)
      - Remote Information Manager (RIM), 1985 (Box 174)
      - Requests, 1982 (Box 174)
      - Research Library Group (RLG)
        - General, 1982-1984 (Box 174)
        - Board of Governors, 27th Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 174)
        - East Asian Program, 1979-1980 (Box 174)
        - Map On-line Users Group, 1980 (Box 174)
        - Research Libraries Information Network (RLIN) Tapes/Peter Ward, 1981-1982 (Box 174)
      - Southeastern League of Michigan Libraries (SEMLOL), 1982-1987; 2 folders (Box 174)
      - Serials Conversion Project, 1979-1983; 2 folders (Box 174)
      - Short Term Cataloging (STC), 1986-1987 (Box 174)
      - Software Policy Taskforce, 1985 (Box 174)
      - Task Force to Study Environments in the Graduate and Undergraduate Libraries, 1979-1981 (Box 174)
      - 3M Corporation, 1985-1985 (Box 174)
      - Title II-C, Higher Education Act, 1978-1987 (Box 174)
      - Title VI, Centers, 1982 (Box 174)
      - University Microfilms International (UMI), 1983-1984 (Box 174)
      - Visitors, 1984 (Box 174)
      - Wayne State University, 1985-1988 (Box 174)
      - Wisconsin, University of, 1981-1984
    - 1957-1989
      The Director's Office Files contain files of three directors: Frederick H. Wagman, Richard M. Dougherty, and Robert M. Warner. All of these files are in an alphabetical topical arrangement. Of particular note in the Wagman files are library organizational charts spanning 1962-1977 and seven folders of Staff Circulars. These circulars provide documentation into library policies and procedures and the changes that evolved in them over the tenure of Wagman's directorship.
      The files of Richard M. Dougherty encompass the largest portion of this series. The content of the files is varied, covering a wide range of library topics and issues. Perhaps the greatest interest can be found in the six Serials Differential Pricing folders. These illustrate the approach the University Library took with regard to rising serials prices. Dougherty was one of the leaders nationally in addressing this issue in libraries.
      The files of Robert M. Warner are comprised of three brief topical files.
      - Frederick H. Wagman
        - Topical Files
          - Divisional Library Surveys, 1971-1976 (Box 198)
          - Funding, 1977-1978 (Box 198)
          - Library Peer Study, 1975-1977 (Box 198)
          - Memoranda, Internal Library, 1957-1977 (Box 198)
          - Organizational Charts, 1962-1977; 2 folders (Box 198)
          - Staff Circulars, 7 folders (Box 198)
      - Richard M. Dougherty
        - Topical Files
          - Book Funding, 1988 (Box 198)
          - Budget/Supplemental Requests, 1985-1989; 4 folders (Box 198)
          - Center for Research Libraries, 1985-1987 (Box 198)
          - Collection Budget, 1986 (Box 198)
          - Correspondence
            - External, 1979-1988; 5 folders (Box 198)
            - Internal
              - Library, 1981-1986; 2 folders (Box 198)
              - University of Michigan, 1982-1987 (Box 198)
          - Funding/Trends, 1977-1978 (Box 198)
          - Grant Proposals, 1985-1988; 2 folders (Box 198)
          - Information Science Archive, 1985-1989 (Box 199)
          - Proposals, 1986 (Box 199)
          - Reports (Miscellaneous), 1985-1987 (Box 199)
          - Serials Differential Pricing, 1985-1988; 6 folders (Box 199)
          - Staff Reports (Miscellaneous), 1987-1988 (Box 199)
          - User Confidentiality, 1987-1988 (Box 199)
      - Robert M. Warner
        - Topical Files
          - Correspondence (Miscellaneous), 1988-1989 (Box 199)
          - Grant Proposals, 1988 (Box 199)
          - Science Libraries, 1988-1989
    - 1978-1997, 1988-1995
      The Director's Topical Files, 1978-1997 (bulk 1988-1995) (13.5 linear feet) consist of records maintained centrally in the administrative suite of the library director/dean. The date ranges span the tenures of four directors (Richard Dougherty, Robert Warner, Donald Riggs, and the beginning of William Gosling's tenure). The bulk of the records are from the directorships of Warner and Riggs. Arranged in a single alphabetical run, the records illuminate the management of one of the ten largest research libraries in the country, with 350 employees, several divisional libraries, and a budget of over $20 million in the mid-1990s.
      Notable themes covered within these records include the implementation of the online catalog (MIRLYN), expanding digital content and access, rising journal subscription costs, construction of the Information Technology Instruction Center (later Media Union) on North Campus, and staff and campus-wide diversity initiatives. Documentation of several key committees is found under the heading, "Library Governance," including the Dean's Cabinet, Library Council, and Management Advisory Council. These forums helped to establish and review policies as well as the allocation of staff and financial resources. Development files showcase efforts to aggressively raise funds to support the work of the library. One of the key development initiatives culminated in the creation of an endowed curator position for Judaica collections. The records also reflect involvement with state groups such as the Michigan Library Consortium, as well as national organizations such as the Research Library Group (RLG).
      - Access Services, Collection Management, Electronic Resources (ACE), 1994-1996 (Box 205)
      - Accounts, 1995-1996 (Box 205)
      - Administration, 1981-1992 (Box 205)
      - African-American Library Staff Association, 1994-1995 (Box 205)
      - Annual Report, 1988-1994 (Box 205)
      - Assisting the Library's Managers Task Force, 1994 (Box 205)
      - Association of Research Libraries (ARL), 1995-1996 (Box 205)
      - Award Committee (Staff Recognition), 1993-1996 (Box 205)
      - Book Theft, 1991 (Box 205)
      - Borrowing Privileges and Fees (Non-University Affiliated), 1988-1991 (Box 205)
      - Budget, 1981/82-1994/95; 14 folders (Box 205)
      - Buhr Building (Preservation and Storage), 1978-1996; 3 folders (Box 206)
      - Business and Finance Office, 1987-1996 (Box 206)
      - Card Catalog, 1994-1995 (Box 206)
      - Center for Research Libraries, 1986-1990 (Box 206)
      - Classification Evaluation Committee, 1981-1996; 2 folders (Box 206)
      - Collection Management Development Council (CMDC), 1990-1993 (Box 206)
      - College of Engineering, 1984-1991 (Box 206)
      - College of Literature, Science and the Arts, 1987-1992 (Box 206)
      - Commission on Preservation and Access, 1995-1996 (Box 206)
      - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC)
        - General, 1987-1996; 7 folders (Box 206)
        - General, 1995-1996 (Box 207)
        - Proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 207)
        - Virtual Electronic Library, 1995-1996 (Box 207)
      - Cooperative Access Services, 1986-1996; 4 folders (Box 207)
      - Correspondence
        - General, 1991-1995 (Box 207)
        - External, 1988-1990 (Box 207)
        - Legislative, 1989; 1994 (Box 207)
        - Library, 1987-1990 (Box 207)
        - University of Michigan, 1988-1990 (Box 207)
      - Cost Studies
        - General, 1982-1988 (Box 207)
        - 1984 Library Cost Study (Submitted to the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services), June 1984 (Box 207)
        - Final Report: The University of Michigan 1984 Library Cost Study, September 1985, 1984-1985 (Box 207)
        - Peat Marwick Study
          - General, 1991-1994 (Box 207)
          - Final Report Volumes 1-4 (Box 208)
      - Council of Library Directors of State Colleges and Universities, 1987-1995; 4 folders (Box 208)
      - Development
        - General, 1984-1994; 6 folders (Box 208)
        - General, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 209)
        - Judaica Collection, 1988-1995 (Box 209)
        - Turkish American Cultural Association, 1994 (Box 209)
      - Differential Pricing (Serials), 1988-1992 (Box 209)
      - Digital Library Initiative, 1993-1996; 2 folders
        - JSTOR (Journal Storage), 1995 (Box 209)
        - Making of America (MOA), 1996 (Box 209)
      - Director's Update, 1989-1990; 1992 (Box 209)
      - Diversity
        - General, 1989-1996; 2 folders (Box 209)
        - Diversity Action Plan Task Force, 1994 (Box 209)
        - Diversity Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 209)
        - Sexual Orientation, 1990 (Box 209)
      - Divisional Libraries
        - General, 1984-1994 (Box 209)
        - Art & Architecture Library, 1985-1993 (Box 209)
        - Asia Library, 1983-1995 (Box 209)
        - Business Administration Library, 1984-1995 (Box 209)
        - Chemistry Library, 1984-1995 (Box 209)
        - Dentistry Library, 1978-1993 (Box 209)
        - Detroit Branch, 1982; 1985 (Box 209)
        - Engineering Basic Science Clusters, 1994-1995 (Box 209)
        - Engineering and Transportation Library, 1982-1992; 1996; 2 folders (Box 209)
        - Fine Arts Library, 1985-1987 (Box 209)
        - Health Science Clusters, 1989-1992 (Box 209)
        - Information and Library Science Library, 1982-1992 (Box 209)
        - Law Library, 1988-1997
          - Greensboro Papers, 1989 (Box 209)
        - Map Library, 1982-1987 (Box 210)
        - Mathematics Library, 1985-1992 (Box 210)
        - Museums Library, 1981-1990 (Box 210)
        - Music Library, 1974-1996 (Box 210)
        - Natural Science and Natural Resources Library, 1992 (Box 210)
        - North Engineering (See Also ITIC), 1983-1990 (Box 210)
        - Physics and Astronomy Library, 1984-1989 (Box 210)
        - Public Health Library, 1981-1988 (Box 210)
        - Science Library, 1983-1996; 2 folders (Box 210)
        - Social Work Library, 1986-1996; 2 folders (Box 210)
        - Taubman Library (Medicine), 1981-1996; 2 folders (Box 210)
      - Document Delivery Advisory Committee (Library of Michigan), 1991-1992 (Box 210)
      - Eastman, Ann Heidbreder Award, 1994-1996 (Box 210)
      - Electronic Database Issues, 1989-1990 (Box 210)
      - Facilities Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 210)
      - Faxon Agreement, 1995 (Box 210)
      - Film and Video Library, 1990; undated (Box 210)
      - Focus Group Project, 1990 (Box 210)
      - Friends of the Library, 1985-1996; 4 folders (Box 210)
      - Gift Correspondence (Mainly Book Donations), 1987-1994 (Box 211)
      - Graduate Library, 1982-1993; 1995-1996; 3 folders (Box 211)
      - Graduate Library Fire, 1993 (Box 211)
      - Grants and Proposals, 1992-1995 (Box 211)
      - How to Make the Library a Better Place to Work (Staff Input), 1993 (Box 211)
      - Human Resources/Personnel, 1988-1996; 3 folders (Box 211)
      - Humanistic Scholars Project, 1981-1987 (Box 211)
      - Information Symposium, 1990-1992 (Box 211)
      - Information Systems Integration for the Health Sciences, 1988-1993
        - IAIMS (Integrated Academic Information Management Systems), 1986-1988 (Box 211)
      - Information Technology Division, 1985; 1990-1993 (Box 211)
      - Information Technology Policy Committee, 1987-1995; 9 folders (Box 211)
      - Integrated Library System (Automation), 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box 212)
      - Integrated Technology Instruction Center (ITIC) Media Union
        - 1986-1990, 1993-1996; 4 folders (Box 212)
        - Cohen Consulting Report on North Campus, 1986 (Box 212)
        - ITIC Interim Report, 1989 (Box 212)
      - Inter-Library Loan, 1986-1996 (Box 212)
      - International Activities, 1989-1998 (Box 212)
      - International Initiatives, 1993-1996 (Box 212)
      - Journal Subscription Cancellations, 1992 (Box 212)
      - Librarian's Forum, 1991-1996; 2 folders (Box 212)
      - Library Area Programs, 1993-1994 (Box 212)
      - Library Director Position, 1988-1990 (Box 212)
      - Library Ergonomics Task Force Report, 1995 (Box 212)
      - Library Fellows Program in International Studies, 1995 (Box 212)
      - Library Governance (University of Michigan)
        - Cabinet
          - Agendas, 1986-1994 (Box 212)
          - Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 212)
        - Dean's/Director's Assembly, 1986-1995; 6 folders (Box 212)
        - Libraries Advisory Committee, 1984-1995; 9 folders (Box 213)
        - Library Council, 1982-1995; 10 folders (Box 213)
        - Management Advisory Council, 1987-1990; 2 folders (Box 213)
      - Library Minority Training Program, 1993-1994 (Box 213)
      - Library of Congress
        - General, 1989 (Box 213)
        - Geography Glass Slides (George Kish), 1987-1989 (Box 213)
        - Remote Access Online User Pilot, 1990 (Box 213)
      - Library Services and Technology Act, 1996 (Box 213)
      - M Link, 1992-1996 (Box 213)
      - M Quality (Total Quality Management), 1993-1996 (Box 213)
      - McGregor Fund for Preservation, 1987-1993 (Box 213)
      - Management Review, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 214)
      - MARC Holdings/Security Team Final Report, 1995 (Box 214)
      - Mass Deacidification (CIC Report), 1992; 3 volumes (Box 214)
      - Merit Review Process, 1988 (Box 214)
      - Merit Review Task Force, 1994 (Box 214)
      - Michigan Information Transfer Source (MITS), 1988-1997 (Box 214)
      - Michigan Library Association (MLA), 1995-1996 (Box 214)
      - Michigan Library Consortium (MLC), 1995-1996 (Box 214)
      - Michigan Newspaper Project, 1992-1995 (Box 214)
      - Michigan Research Library Triangle (MRLT), 1991-1996; 4 folders (Box 214)
      - MIRLYN, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box 214)
      - National Coordinated Cataloging Program (Library of Congress), 1987-1992 (Box 214)
      - Newsletters and Publicity, 1987-1990; 1995-1996 (Box 214)
      - NOTIS, 1991-1994 (Box 214)
      - On-line Search Services, 1987-1988 (Box 214)
      - Organizational Charts, 1985-1998 (Box 214)
      - Papyrology, 1990-1996 (Box 215)
      - Patron Record Privacy, 1988 (Box 215)
      - Policies, 1986-1992 (Box 215)
      - Preservation, 1989-1995 (Box 215)
      - Professional valuation Review Committee (PERC), 1985-1987 (Box 215)
      - Public Services, 1989-1996; 3 folders (Box 215)
      - Questionnaires, 1988-1997 (Box 215)
      - Research and Creative Project Funding Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 215)
      - Research Library Fellows, 1991-1993 (Box 215)
      - Research Library Group (RLG)
        - Correspondence, 1985-1987; 6 folders (Box 215)
        - Correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box 215)
        - Bibtech, 1981-1991 (Box 215)
        - Carnegie Study on Distributed Processing, 1983-1984 (Box 215)
        - Collection Development and Resources Sharing, 1983-1992 (Box 215)
        - Electronic Mail, 1987-1991
        - International Conference, 1986 (Box 216)
        - Presidents Meeting, 1986-1996 (Box 216)
        - Recon, 1982-1988 (Box 216)
        - Retreat on RLG, 1989 (Box 216)
        - RLG-Michigan Finances, 1980-1986 (Box 216)
        - Transition, 1991 (Box 216)
      - Research Library Residency Program, 1982-1997; 3 folders (Box 216)
      - Rosenthal, Samuel and Marie-Louise, 1986-1994 (Box 216)
      - Scholarly Communication Project (journal editors at UM), 1988 (Box 216)
      - School of Information and Library Science(SILS)/Library Educational Program, 1989-1990 (Box 216)
      - Second European Conference on Archives (includes photos), 1988 (Box 216)
      - Security Team, 1995-1996 (Box 216)
      - Senate, 1995-1996 (Box 216)
      - 747-FAST Service, 1986-1992 (Box 216)
      - Shapiro Library Dedication, 1994-1995 (Box 216)
      - Special Collections
        - General, 1988-1997; 3 folders (Box 216)
        - Information Science Archives
          - General, 1986-1988 (Box 216)
          - Benton, Charles, 1987 (Box 216)